villabertolli.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Bertolli

Skip to content

  * English
  * Spanish

### MIZKAN AMERICA, INC. PRIVACY PRINCIPLES

Mizkan America, Inc. takes privacy seriously. The following four principles underpin our approach to respecting your privacy:

  1. We value the trust that you place in us by giving us your personal information. We will always use your personal information in a way that is fair and worthy of that trust.
  2. We will provide clear information about how we use your personal information. We shall always be transparent with you about what information we collect, what we do with it, with whom we share it and who you should contact if you have any concerns.
  3. We will take all reasonable steps to protect your information from misuse and keep it secure.
  4. We will comply with all applicable data protection laws and regulations and we will co-operate with data protection authorities. In the absence of data protection legislation, we will act in accordance with generally accepted principles governing data protection.

### MIZKAN AMERICA, INC. PRIVACY NOTICE

_Last Updated: December 2014_

This Privacy Notice explains the types of personal information we collect and how we use, disclose and protect that information.

### What does this Privacy Notice apply to?

This Privacy Notice applies to personal information collected by Mizkan America, Inc. in connection with the brands we offer (find out more about Mizkan America, Inc. at <http://www.mizkan.com/Corporate.aspx>. This includes information collected offline through our Consumer Support Centers, direct marketing campaigns, sweepstakes and competitions, and online through our websites, applications and branded pages on third-party platforms and applications accessed or used through such websites or third-party platforms (“ **Mizkan Americas** **Sites** ”).

This Privacy Notice also applies to targeted Mizkan America, Inc. content, including offers and advertisements for Mizkan America, Inc. products and services, which we (or a service provider acting on our behalf) may send to you on third-party websites, platforms and applications ( **“Third-Party Sites”** ) based on your Site Usage Information (as defined below). These Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies and terms and conditions. We encourage you to read them before using those Third-Party Sites.

This Privacy Notice is hereby incorporated into and forms part of the terms and conditions of use of the applicable Mizkan America, Inc. Site. **See your privacy rights and who to contact** **below**.

### Your consent

By using a Mizkan America, Inc. Site, you are consenting to the relevant Mizkan America, Inc. brand collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in this way, please do not use Mizkan America, Inc. Sites with your personal information.

Mizkan America, Inc. will only collect, use or disclose your personal information where it is fair and lawful to do so. If required by applicable data protection laws, we will ask for your consent explicitly before collecting, using or sharing your personal information.  In other cases, and if permitted by applicable data protection laws, we may infer your consent from your actions and behavior. We may ask you to provide additional consent if we need to use your personal information for purposes not covered by this Privacy Notice. You are not obliged to provide such consent but if you decide not to then your participation in certain activities may be restricted. If you provide additional consent, the terms of that consent shall prevail in the event of any conflict with the terms of this Privacy Notice.

Please note, however, that we may process your personal information without consent if we have a legitimate reason to do so, provided that such use will not have a prejudicial effect on your own rights, freedoms and interests. Any such use shall be in accordance with the Mizkan America, Inc. Privacy Principles set out above.

### What about my child’s privacy?

Websites operated by or on behalf of Mizkan America, Inc. are intended for use by persons age 13 and over. Mizkan America, Inc. does not seek to collect information about children under the age of 13. No information should be submitted to or posted on Mizkan America, Inc.’s websites by users under 13 years of age.

If a child under the age of 13 submits personal information to Mizkan America, Inc.’s website, we delete the information as soon as we discover it was provided by a child under 13 years of age and do not use it for any purpose. Mizkan America, Inc. encourages parents to take an active role in their children’s use of the Internet and to inform them of the potential dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet.

### What information do we collect?

In this Privacy Notice, your “personal information” means information or pieces of information that could allow you to be identified. This typically includes information such as your name, address, screen name, profile picture, email address, and telephone number, but can also include other information such as IP address, shopping habits, information about your lifestyle or preferences such as your hobbies and interests. We may collect personal information about you from different sources, including:

  1. Information you give us directly
  2. Information you consent or direct us to share with our service providers or partners
  3. Information we collect automatically when you use the Mizkan America, Inc. Sites
  4. Information we collect from other sources

### How do we use your personal information?

We use your personal information to:

  1. Improve our products and your experience on the Mizkan America, Inc. Sites.
  2. To contact you regarding products and services which may be of interest to you, provided you have given us consent to do so or you have previously requested a product or service from us and the communication is relevant or related to that prior request and made within any timeframes established by applicable laws.
  3. To provide you with products or services that you request from us.
  4. To send you informational or promotional communications that you have requested to receive.

### Cookies

We use “cookies” on our Sites. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Sites. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Sites. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our Sites.

### Mobile Messaging Services

We may make available a service through which you can receive text or other types of messages from Mizkan America, Inc. (such as SMS (short message service), or MMS (multimedia message service), or EMS (enhanced message service)), or push notifications on your wireless or mobile device (“Mobile Message Service”). If you subscribe to one of our Mobile Message Services, we will expressly ask you to agree to receiving such messages from Mizkan America, Inc. at the address or mobile number you provide for that purpose (unless and until you have elected to opt out of receiving such messages by following the instructions in the  **Your privacy rights and who to contact**  section below or by changing the settings on your mobile device).

You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the  **Your privacy rights and who to contact**  section below. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, you agree that we may collect from you and provide your carrier with your applicable payment information in connection therewith. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device you use to sign up for the Mobile Message Service, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. In addition to meeting certain age restrictions and any other terms and conditions associated with each Mobile Message Service, you may be required to register personal information such as your name, text message, wireless address or mobile phone number. We may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the Mobile Message Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our Mobile Message Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note, however, that your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

You acknowledge and agree that the Mobile Message Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the Mobile Message Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the Mobile Message Service. We may also access the content of your wireless and/or mobile phone account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and/or service-related complaints.

### Who do we share your personal information with?

Mizkan America, Inc. is an operating unit of Mizkan Americas, Inc., the pre-eminent manufacturer and marketer of specialty vinegars, mustards, cooking wines, marinades, wine reductions, salted spirits, Asian sauces and dressings, and a variety of other liquid condiments. See more at: <http://www.mizkan.com/Corporate.aspx>. Mizkan America, Inc. may share your personal information with the member companies of the Mizkan Group and trusted third-parties based outside the country in which you live so that they may process that data on our behalf.

We may also share your personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Mizkan America, Inc. if we believe that disclosure of the information is necessary for legal reasons.

### Transferring your personal information

We may transfer your personal information to servers located outside the country in which you live or to affiliates or other trusted third-parties based in other countries so that they may process personal information on our behalf. By using a Mizkan America, Inc. Site or otherwise providing Mizkan America, Inc. with personal information, you agree to us doing so in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Notice and applicable data protection laws and regulations.

You should be aware that many countries do not afford the same legal protection to personal information as you might enjoy in your country of origin. While your personal information is in another country, it may be accessed by the courts, law enforcement and national security authorities in that country in accordance with its laws. Subject to such lawful access requests, we promise that anyone processing your personal information outside your country of origin is required to implement measures to protect it and is only entitled to process it in accordance with Mizkan America, Inc.’s instructions.

### Safeguarding your personal information

We take all reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure and require any third-parties that handle or process your personal information for us to do the same. Access to your personal information is restricted to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse and is only permitted among our employees and agents on a need-to-know basis.

### Your privacy rights and who to contact

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about how we handle your personal information, then you may contact us by clicking the **Contact Us** link on the Mizkan America, Inc. Site that directed you to this Privacy Notice. Your request will be directed to the appropriate Mizkan America, Inc. brand. Alternatively, please go to www.mizkan.com and click on the **Contact Us** link.

You have the right to tell us if you:

  1. Don’t want to be contacted in the future by us
  2. Would like a copy of the personal information which we hold about you
  3. Would like us to correct, update or delete your personal information in our records
  4. Wish to report any misuse of your personal information

To assist us in dealing with your request, please provide your full name and details.

### Changes to our Privacy Notice

We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time by posting the updated version of the Privacy Policy on the Mizkan America, Inc. Sites. We will give you reasonable notice of any material change. We encourage you to visit frequently to stay informed about how we use your personal information.

### Other Mizkan America, Inc. privacy notices

In addition to this Privacy Notice, there may be specific campaigns or promotions which will be governed by additional privacy terms or policies. We encourage you to read these additional terms or policies before participating in any such campaigns or promotions as you will be required to comply with them if you participate. Any additional privacy terms or policies will be made prominently available to you.

### PRINCIPIOS DE PRIVACIDAD DE R&B FOODS, INC.

R&B Foods, Inc. se toma en serio la privacidad. Los cuatro principios que figuran a continuación sustentan el método que adoptamos para respetar su privacidad:

  1. Valoramos que confíe en nosotros y que nos brinde su información personal. Siempre utilizaremos su información personal de forma justa y digna de esa confianza.
  2. Proporcionaremos información clara sobre cómo utilizar su información personal. Siempre seremos transparentes con usted sobre la información que recolectamos, lo que hacemos con ella, con quién la compartimos y con quién debería comunicarse si tiene alguna inquietud.
  3. Tomaremos todos los pasos que sean razonables para proteger su información del uso indebido y para mantenerla segura.
  4. Cumpliremos con todas las leyes y regulaciones de protección de datos aplicables, y cooperaremos con las autoridades de protección de datos. Ante la falta de legislación sobre protección de datos, actuaremos de acuerdo con los principios generalmente aceptados que rigen la protección de datos.

### AVISO DE PRIVACIDAD DE R&B FOODS, INC.

_Fecha de la última actualización: diciembre de 2014_  
Este Aviso de privacidad explica los tipos de información personal que recopilamos y cómo utilizamos, divulgamos y protegemos esa información.

### ¿A qué se aplica este Aviso de privacidad?

Este Aviso de privacidad se aplica a la información personal que recopila R&B Foods, Inc. en relación con las marcas que ofrecemos (obtenga más información sobre R&B Foods, Inc. en <http://www.mizkan.com/Corporate.aspx>. Esto incluye información recopilada fuera de línea a través de nuestros Centros de atención al consumidor, campañas de marketing directo, sorteos y competencias, y en línea a través de nuestros sitios web, aplicaciones y páginas de las marcas alojadas en plataformas externas y aplicaciones a las cuales se puede acceder o utilizar a través de tales sitios web o plataformas externas (“ **Sitios de Mizkan Americas** ”).

Este Aviso de privacidad también se aplica al contenido objetivo de R&B Foods, Inc., que incluye ofertas y publicidades de los productos y servicios de R&B Foods, Inc., que nosotros (o un proveedor de servicios que actúe en nuestro nombre) podemos enviarle a usted a través de sitios web, plataformas y aplicaciones externos ( **“Sitios externos”** ) según su Información de uso del sitio (como se define a continuación). Es probable que estos Sitios externos tengan sus propias políticas y términos y condiciones de privacidad. Lo alentamos a leerlas antes de utilizar tales Sitios externos.

Este aviso de privacidad se incorpora al presente documento y forma parte de los términos y condiciones de uso del sitio de R&B Foods, Inc. correspondiente. Consulte la sección  **Sus derechos de privacidad y con quién debe comunicarse**  a continuación.

### Su consentimiento

Al utilizar un sitio de R&B Foods, Inc., otorga su consentimiento para que la marca relevante de R&B Foods, Inc. recopile, use y divulgue su información personal, de acuerdo con este Aviso de privacidad. Si no está de acuerdo con esta forma de recopilación, uso y divulgación de su información personal, no utilice los sitios de R&B Foods, Inc. con su información personal.  
R&B Foods, Inc. solo recolectará, utilizará o divulgará su información personal en los casos en que resulte justo y legal hacerlo. En la mayoría de los casos, le solicitaremos explícitamente su consentimiento, pero en algunos casos, podríamos inferir su consentimiento a partir de sus acciones y su comportamiento. Probablemente le solicitemos que otorgue un consentimiento adicional si necesitamos utilizar su información personal para fines que no están cubiertos por este Aviso de privacidad. Usted no está obligado a otorgar tal consentimiento, pero si decide no hacerlo, es probable que se restrinja su participación en ciertas actividades. Si otorga el consentimiento adicional, regirán los términos de ese consentimiento en caso de producirse algún conflicto con los términos de este Aviso de privacidad.  
Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que probablemente procesemos su información personal sin su consentimiento, si tenemos un motivo legítimo para hacerlo, siempre que tal uso no perjudique sus propios derechos, libertades e intereses. Tales usos deberán realizarse de acuerdo con los Principios de privacidad de R&B Foods, Inc. establecidos anteriormente.

### ¿Qué sucede con la privacidad de mi hijo?

Los sitios web operados por R&B Foods, Inc. o en su nombre fueron diseñados para ser utilizados por personas mayores de 13 años. R&B Foods, Inc. no busca recopilar información sobre niños menores de 13 años. Los usuarios menores de 13 años no deben enviar ni publicar ninguna información en los sitios web de R&B Foods, Inc.

Si un niño menor de 13 años envía información personal al sitio web de R&B Foods, Inc., nosotros eliminamos la información en cuanto descubrimos que fue proporcionada por un niño menor de 13 años y no la utilizamos para ningún fin. R&B Foods, Inc. alienta a los padres a adoptar un rol activo en el uso que hacen sus hijos de Internet y a informarles sobre los posibles peligros de brindar información sobre ellos en Internet.

### ¿Qué información recopilamos?

En este Aviso de privacidad, su “información personal” hace referencia a la información o a las piezas de información que podrían identificarle. Esto generalmente incluye información, como su nombre, dirección, nombre de usuario, imagen de perfil, dirección de correo electrónico y número de teléfono, pero también incluye otra información, como dirección IP, hábitos de consumo, información sobre su estilo de vida o preferencias, como sus pasatiempos e intereses. Probablemente recopilemos información sobre usted de diferentes fuentes, que incluyen:

  1. Información que usted nos proporciona directamente.
  2. Información que recopilamos automáticamente cuando usted utiliza los sitios de R&B Foods, Inc.
  3. Información que recopilamos de otras fuentes.

### ¿Cómo usamos su información personal?

Usamos su información personal para:

  1. Mejorar nuestros productos y su experiencia en los sitios de R&B Foods, Inc.
  2. Comunicarnos con usted por los productos y servicios que puedan interesarle, siempre que nos haya otorgado su consentimiento para hacerlo o nos haya solicitado previamente un producto o servicio y la comunicación resulte relevante, o esté relacionada con esa solicitud previa, y se realice dentro de los plazos establecidos por las leyes aplicables.
  3. Brindarle productos o servicios que nos haya solicitado.

### Cookies

En nuestros sitios utilizamos “cookies”. Una cookie es una pieza de información que se almacena en el disco rígido del visitante de un sitio para ayudarnos a mejorar su acceso a nuestro sitio y a identificar a los visitantes que frecuentemente ingresan a nuestro sitio. De hecho, cuando utilizamos una cookie para identificarlo, usted no tendría que ingresar una contraseña más de una vez, lo cual le permitiría ahorrar tiempo mientras visita nuestros sitios. Las cookies también pueden permitirnos realizar un seguimiento y concentrarnos en los intereses de nuestros usuarios para mejorar la experiencia en nuestros sitios. El uso de una cookie de ninguna manera está relacionado con la información personal que lo identifica en nuestros sitios.

### Servicios de mensajes móviles

Es probable que pongamos a disposición un servicio a través del cual pueda recibir mensajes de texto u otros tipos de mensajes de R&B Foods, Inc. (como el servicio de mensajes cortos [short message service, SMS], el servicio de mensajes multimedia [multimedia message service, MMS] o el servicio mejorado de mensajes [enhanced message service, EMS] en su dispositivo inalámbrico o móvil [“Servicio de mensajes móviles”]). Si se suscribe a uno de nuestros Servicios de mensajes móviles, usted acepta recibir dichos mensajes de parte de R&B Foods, Inc. en la dirección o al número de teléfono móvil que proporciona para tal fin (al menos y hasta que haya optado por no recibir dichos mensajes al seguir las instrucciones incluidas en la sección  **Sus derechos de privacidad y con quién debe comunicarse**  que figura a continuación).  
Usted comprende que a estos mensajes se aplican las tasas estándares de su compañía de servicios inalámbricos y que puede cambiar de parecer en cualquier momento, solo con seguir las instrucciones incluidas en la sección  **Sus derechos de privacidad y con quién debe comunicarse**  que figura a continuación. En caso de cobrarse cargos en la factura de su cuenta inalámbrica, usted acepta que nosotros le cobremos y proporcionemos a su compañía su información del pago correspondiente relacionada. Usted manifiesta que es el propietario o usuario autorizado del dispositivo inalámbrico que utiliza para inscribirse al Servicio de mensajes móviles, y que está autorizado a aprobar los cargos correspondientes. Además de cumplir con ciertas restricciones de edad y con otros términos y condiciones relacionados con cada Servicio de mensajes móviles, probablemente deba registrar información personal, como su nombre, mensaje de texto, dirección inalámbrica o número de teléfono móvil. También es probable que obtengamos la fecha, la hora y el contenido de sus mensajes mientras utiliza el Servicio de mensajes móviles. La información que obtengamos en relación con nuestro Servicio de mensajes móviles la utilizaremos conforme a esta Política de privacidad. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que su compañía de servicios inalámbricos y otros proveedores de servicios también pueden recopilar datos sobre el uso que usted hace de su dispositivo inalámbrico, y que sus prácticas se rigen por sus propias políticas.  
Usted reconoce y acepta que el Servicio de mensajes móviles se proporciona a través de sistemas inalámbricos que usan radios (y otros medios) para transmitir comunicaciones por redes complejas. No garantizamos que el uso que usted hace del Servicio de mensajes móviles sea privado ni seguro, y no nos responsabilizamos frente a usted por ninguna falta de privacidad o de seguridad que pueda experimentar. Usted será absolutamente responsable de tomar las precauciones y de proporcionar las medidas de seguridad que mejor se adapten a su situación y al uso que pretende hacer del Servicio de mensajes móviles. Además, es probable que, con su compañía, tengamos acceso al contenido de su cuenta inalámbrica y/o del teléfono móvil con el objeto de identificar y resolver problemas técnicos y/o quejas relacionadas con el servicio.

### ¿Con quién compartimos su información personal?

R&B Foods, Inc. es una unidad operativa de Mizkan Americas, el fabricante preeminente y comercializador de vinagres especiales, mostazas, vinos para cocinar, marinadas, reducciones de vino, licores salados, salsas y aderezos asiáticos y una variedad de otros condimentos líquidos. Consulte más información en: <http://www.mizkan.com/Corporate.aspx>. R&B Foods, Inc. podría compartir su información personal con las compañías miembro del Mizkan Group y con terceros confiables que se encuentren ubicados fuera del país en el que usted vive de modo tal que puedan procesar esos datos en nuestro nombre.

También podríamos compartir su información personal con compañías, organizaciones o personas ajenas a R&B Foods, Inc. si consideramos que la divulgación de su información resulta necesaria por motivos legales.

### Cómo se transfiere su información personal

Podríamos transferir su información personal a servidores ubicados fuera del país donde vive o a filiales u otros terceros confiables que se encuentran en otros países, para que puedan procesar la información personal en nuestro nombre. Al utilizar un sitio de R&B Foods, Inc. o de otro modo brindarle información personal a R&B Foods, Inc., usted acepta que lo hagamos conforme a los términos de este Aviso de privacidad y a las leyes y regulaciones de protección de datos correspondientes.  
Debe ser consciente de que varios países no ofrecen la misma protección legal de la información personal que usted podría gozar en su país de origen. Si bien su información personal se encuentra en otro país, es probable que los tribunales, las autoridades de seguridad nacional y del cumplimiento de la ley de ese país accedan a ella de acuerdo con sus leyes. Sujeto a dichas solicitudes de acceso legal, nosotros le prometemos que exigiremos a cualquier persona que procese su información personal fuera de su país de origen la implementación de medidas para protegerla y que solo tendrá derecho a procesarla de acuerdo con las indicaciones de R&B Foods, Inc.

### Cómo se protege su información personal

Tomamos todas las precauciones razonables para mantener segura su información personal y exigimos a los terceros que manejan o procesan su información personal por nosotros a que hagan lo mismo. El acceso a su información personal es restringido a fin de evitar el acceso no autorizado, la modificación o el uso indebido, y solo está permitido a nuestros empleados y agentes, cuando necesiten conocerla.

### Sus derechos de privacidad y con quién debe comunicarse

Si tiene alguna pregunta, comentario o inquietud sobre cómo manejar su información personal, puede comunicarse con nosotros al hacer clic en el enlace  **Contact Us**  (Contacto) del sitio de R&B Foods, Inc., el cual lo dirigirá hasta este Aviso de privacidad. Su solicitud se dirigirá a la marca correspondiente de R&B Foods, Inc. Como alternativa, visite www.mizkan.com y haga clic en el enlace  **Contact Us**.

Usted tiene derecho a informarnos si:

  1. No desea que nos comuniquemos con usted en el futuro.
  2. Desearía obtener una copia de la información personal que conservamos sobre usted.
  3. Le gustaría que corrijamos, actualicemos o eliminemos su información personal que figura en nuestros registros.
  4. Desea denunciar algún uso indebido de su información personal.

Para ayudarnos a lidiar con su solicitud, indíquenos su nombre completo y los detalles.

### Cambios en nuestro Aviso de privacidad

Es probable que, oportunamente, realicemos cambios en este Aviso de privacidad y que publiquemos su versión actualizada en los sitios de R&B Foods, Inc. Le notificaremos razonablemente cualquier modificación material. Lo alentamos a visitar este Aviso con frecuencia para mantenerse informado sobre cómo utilizamos su información personal.

### Otros avisos de privacidad de R&B Foods, Inc.

Además de este Aviso de privacidad, probablemente existan campañas o promociones específicas que se regirán por otros términos o políticas de privacidad. Lo alentamos a leer estos términos o políticas adicionales antes de participar en alguna de esas campañas o promociones, dado que deberá cumplir con ellos si participa. Cualquier término o política de privacidad adicional se pondrá a su disposición de forma eminente.

## Claim your seat at the table

Sign up for our email list to receive future Bertolli® coupons, recipes and more.

Sign Up

_You can opt out at any time. View  our Privacy Policy._

### select your bertolli® experience

Customers all over the world choose Bertolli® for Italian-inspired recipes and authentic flavor. Continue to our U.S. site or select 'International' below to choose your country. 

[International

](https://www.bertolli.com/international/)

[continue to U.S.

](https://www.bertolli.com/)

Would you like to disconnect your Facebook account from our website? Your favorites will no longer be saved across devices.

Would you like to log out of Facebook? Favorites will no longer be saved across devices.

Are you should you wante to disconnect your account?  
All your favorites will be deleted and cannot be restored.

## Save Across Devices

You can't save the aroma of your favorite meal, but you can save the recipe!  
Create an account now to start saving your favorite recipes, products and how-to's across all of your devices.
